<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>CC-BY on Derivatives</title><link>/docs/cc-by/</link><description>Recent content in CC-BY on Derivatives</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="/docs/cc-by/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Creative Commons License Deed Attribution 2.0 Generic (CC BY 2.0)</title><link>/docs/cc-by/cc-by-2-summary/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/cc-by/cc-by-2-summary/</guid><description>Skip to content Share your work Use &amp;amp; remix What We do Blog Search for CC images Global Network Newsletters Store Contact Facebook Twitter Mail Help us build a vibrant, collaborative global commons
This page is available in the following languages: Languages cc logo Attribution 2.0 Generic (CC BY 2.0) This is a human-readable summary of (and not a substitute for) the license. Disclaimer.
You are free to: # Share — copy and redistribute the material in any medium or format Adapt — remix, transform, and build upon the material for any purpose, even commercially.</description></item><item><title>Creative Commons Legal Code Attribution 2.0</title><link>/docs/cc-by/cc-by-2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/cc-by/cc-by-2/</guid><description>Creative Commons Creative Commons Legal Code
Attribution 2.0 # CREATIVE COMMONS CORPORATION IS NOT A LAW FIRM AND DOES NOT PROVIDE LEGAL SERVICES. DISTRIBUTION OF THIS LICENSE DOES NOT CREATE AN ATTORNEY-CLIENT RELATIONSHIP. CREATIVE COMMONS PROVIDES THIS INFORMATION ON AN &amp;ldquo;AS-IS&amp;rdquo; BASIS. CREATIVE COMMONS MAKES NO WARRANTIES REGARDING THE INFORMATION PROVIDED, AND DISCLAIMS LIABILITY FOR DAMAGES RESULTING FROM ITS USE.
License # THE WORK (AS DEFINED BELOW) IS PROVIDED UNDER THE TERMS OF THIS CREATIVE COMMONS PUBLIC LICENSE (&amp;ldquo;CCPL&amp;rdquo; OR &amp;ldquo;LICENSE&amp;rdquo;).</description></item><item><title>Creative Commons License Deed Attribution 3.0 Unported (CC BY 3.0)</title><link>/docs/cc-by/cc-by-3-summary/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/cc-by/cc-by-3-summary/</guid><description>Skip to content Share your work Use &amp;amp; remix What We do Blog Search for CC images Global Network Newsletters Store Contact Facebook Twitter Mail Help us build a vibrant, collaborative global commons This page is available in the following languages: Languages cc logo Attribution 3.0 Unported (CC BY 3.0) This is a human-readable summary of (and not a substitute for) the license. Disclaimer.
You are free to: # Share — copy and redistribute the material in any medium or format Adapt — remix, transform, and build upon the material for any purpose, even commercially.</description></item><item><title>Creative Commons Attribution 3.0 Unported</title><link>/docs/cc-by/cc-by-3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/cc-by/cc-by-3/</guid><description>Creative Commons Legal Code Attribution 3.0 Unported
CREATIVE COMMONS CORPORATION IS NOT A LAW FIRM AND DOES NOT PROVIDE LEGAL SERVICES. DISTRIBUTION OF THIS LICENSE DOES NOT CREATE AN ATTORNEY-CLIENT RELATIONSHIP. CREATIVE COMMONS PROVIDES THIS INFORMATION ON AN &amp;ldquo;AS-IS&amp;rdquo; BASIS. CREATIVE COMMONS MAKES NO WARRANTIES REGARDING THE INFORMATION PROVIDED, AND DISCLAIMS LIABILITY FOR DAMAGES RESULTING FROM ITS USE.
License # THE WORK (AS DEFINED BELOW) IS PROVIDED UNDER THE TERMS OF THIS CREATIVE COMMONS PUBLIC LICENSE (&amp;ldquo;CCPL&amp;rdquo; OR &amp;ldquo;LICENSE&amp;rdquo;).</description></item><item><title>Creative Commons License Deed Attribution 4.0 International (CC BY 4.0)</title><link>/docs/cc-by/cc-by-4-summary/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/cc-by/cc-by-4-summary/</guid><description>Skip to content Share your work Use &amp;amp; remix What We do Blog Help us build a vibrant, collaborative global commons
This page is available in the following languages: Languages
cc logo Attribution 4.0 International (CC BY 4.0) This is a human-readable summary of (and not a substitute for) the license. Disclaimer.
You are free to: # Share — copy and redistribute the material in any medium or format Adapt — remix, transform, and build upon the material for any purpose, even commercially.</description></item><item><title>Creative Commons Konzessionsurkunde Namensnennung 4.0 International (CC BY 4.0)</title><link>/docs/cc-by/cc-by-4-de/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/cc-by/cc-by-4-de/</guid><description>Diese Seite ist in folgenden Sprachen verfügbar:
Zum Inhalt überspringen
Teilen Sie Ihre Arbeit Use &amp;amp; remix What We do Blog Search for CC images Global Network Newsletters Store Kontakt Facebook Twitter Mail Helfen Sie uns lebhafte und kollaborative globale Commons zu schaffen.
Diese Seite ist in folgenden Sprachen verfügbar: Languages
cc logo Namensnennung 4.0 International (CC BY 4.0) This is a human-readable summary of (and not a substitute for) the license.</description></item><item><title>Creative Commons Legal Code Attribution 4.0 International</title><link>/docs/cc-by/cc-by-4/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/docs/cc-by/cc-by-4/</guid><description>Share your work Use &amp;amp; remix What we do Blog Global Affiliate Network Search the Commons Contact Facebook Twitter Mail Help us build a vibrant, collaborative global commons
This page is available in the following languages: Languages
CCAttribution
Attribution 4.0 International
Official translations of this license are available in other languages.
Creative Commons Corporation (“Creative Commons”) is not a law firm and does not provide legal services or legal advice. Distribution of Creative Commons public licenses does not create a lawyer-client or other relationship.</description></item></channel></rss>