<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Docs on Derivatives</title><link>localhost:1313/docs/</link><description>Recent content in Docs on Derivatives</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><atom:link href="localhost:1313/docs/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>README</title><link>localhost:1313/docs/readme/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>localhost:1313/docs/readme/</guid><description>Derivatives is an exploration of all things original and copy.
Articles about origins and originality, published here in derivative form, constitute the bulk of this book. Each of these articles has already been published under an open access (CC-BY) license elsewhere. Original publications have been stated on each article.
The aim of this book is to ponder about text reuse, origins and copying&amp;mdash;and why these things appear to bother people so much.</description></item><item><title>Architecture of the Human Origin Recognition Complex*</title><link>localhost:1313/docs/architecture-human-orc/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>localhost:1313/docs/architecture-human-orc/</guid><description>From the Department of Pathology, Brigham and Women’s Hospital, Harvard Medical School, Boston, Massachusetts 02115
Received for publication, April 6, 2001 Published, JBC Papers in Press, June 6, 2001, DOI 10.1074/jbc.M103078200
THE JOURNAL OF BIOLOGICAL CHEMISTRY Vol. 276, No. 31, Issue of August 3, pp. 29067–29071, 2001 © 2001 by The American Society for Biochemistry and Molecular Biology, Inc. Printed in U.S.A.
Skip to main contentSkip to article Elsevier logo Journals &amp; Books Register Sign in View PDF Download full issue Outline MATERIALS AND METHODS RESULTS DISCUSSION Acknowledgments REFERENCES Figures (8) Figure 1.</description></item><item><title>Origins of amyloid-β</title><link>localhost:1313/docs/amyloid-%CE%B2/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>localhost:1313/docs/amyloid-%CE%B2/</guid><description>Skip to main content Advertisement BMC Part of Springer Nature
Search Explore journals Get published About BMC Login BMC Genomics Home About Articles Submission Guidelines Research article Open Access Published: 30 April 2013 Origins of amyloid-β
RESEARCH ARTICLE Open Access
William G Tharp1,2 &amp;amp; Indra Neil Sarkar1,3,4, * BMC Genomics volume 14, Article number: 290 (2013) Cite this article
Tharp and Sarkar BMC Genomics 2013, 14:290 http://www.biomedcentral.com/1471-2164/14/290
* Correspondence: neil.sarkar@uvm.edu</description></item><item><title>Effects of arsenic and heavy metals on metabolic pathways in cells of human origin: Similarities and differences</title><link>localhost:1313/docs/arsenic/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>localhost:1313/docs/arsenic/</guid><description>Skip to main contentSkip to article Elsevier logo Journals &amp;amp; Books Register Sign in View PDF Download full issue Outline Highlights Abstract Graphical abstract Keywords
Introduction Methods and materials Results and discussion Conclusion Statement of ethics Funding sources Author contributions Declaration of Competing Interest Acknowledgement Appendix A. Supplementary data References Show full outline Figures (7) # Unlabelled figure Fig. 1. Pathways that are affected by particular heavy metals irrespective of the cell… Fig.</description></item><item><title>Back to the future: origins and directions of the “Agile Manifesto” – views of the originators</title><link>localhost:1313/docs/back-to-future/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>localhost:1313/docs/back-to-future/</guid><description>Skip to main content Advertisement SpringerOpen
Search Get published Explore Journals Books About Login Journal of Software Engineering Research and Development Articles Research Open Access Published: 09 November 2018 Back to the future: origins and directions of the “Agile Manifesto” – views of the originators
Philipp Hohl, Jil Klünder, Arie van Bennekum, Ryan Lockard, James Gifford, Jürgen Münch, Michael Stupperich &amp;amp; Kurt Schneider Journal of Software Engineering Research and Development volume 6, Article number: 15 (2018) Cite this article</description></item><item><title>Folding, Assembly, and Persistence: The Essential Nature and Origins of Biopolymers</title><link>localhost:1313/docs/biopolymers/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>localhost:1313/docs/biopolymers/</guid><description>Skip to main content Advertisement SpringerLink
Search Log in Original Article Open Access Published: 19 November 2018 Folding, Assembly, and Persistence: The Essential Nature and Origins of Biopolymers
Calvin M. Runnels, Kathryn A. Lanier, Justin Krish Williams, Jessica C. Bowman, Anton S. Petrov, Nicholas V. Hud &amp;amp; Loren Dean Williams Journal of Molecular Evolution volume 86, pages 598–610 (2018)Cite this article
3227 Accesses 20 Citations 16 Altmetric Metrics details
Abstract # Life as we know it requires three basic types of polymers: polypeptide, polynucleotide, and polysaccharide.</description></item><item><title>The nature and origin of Charon's smooth plains</title><link>localhost:1313/docs/charon-smooth-plains/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>localhost:1313/docs/charon-smooth-plains/</guid><description>Skip to main contentSkip to article Elsevier logo Journals &amp;amp; Books Register Sign in View PDF Download full issue View Open Manuscript Outline Highlights Abstract Keywords Keywords: Pluto Charon Geological processes Cryovolcanism Image processing
Introduction Observations Analysis and results Conclusions Acknowledgments Appendix A. References Show full outline Figures (18) Fig. 1. The low elevation Vulcan Planitia extends across the lower portion of the disk,… Fig. 2. Geomorphologic map of Charon features overlain on a mosaic of LORRI images Fig.</description></item><item><title>Origin of the Chinese word for “cell”: an unusual but wonderful idea of a mathematician</title><link>localhost:1313/docs/chinese-word-cell/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>localhost:1313/docs/chinese-word-cell/</guid><description>Skip to main content Advertisement SpringerLink
Search Log in Recollection Open Access Published: 21 September 2020 Origin of the Chinese word for “cell”: an unusual but wonderful idea of a mathematician
He Zhang12✉︎
Protein &amp;amp; Cell volume 12, pages 671–674 (2021)Cite this article
826 Accesses 1 Altmetric Metrics details
In today’s biology and even the whole field of natural science, “cell” is undoubtedly a central concept. Even in everyday life, it is a well-known common word.</description></item><item><title>City origins</title><link>localhost:1313/docs/city-origins/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>localhost:1313/docs/city-origins/</guid><description>Skip to main contentSkip to article Elsevier logo Journals &amp;amp; Books Register Sign in View PDF Outline Highlights Abstract Keywords
Introduction City seeds - an overview Empirical evidence - moving beyond descriptives Expanding empirical possibilities Conclusion Author statement Declaration of competing interest A. Appendix References Show full outline Tables (2) Table 1 Table 2 Elsevier Regional Science and Urban Economics Available online 16 April 2021, 103677 In Press, Corrected ProofWhat are Corrected Proof articles?</description></item><item><title>Counterfeit versus original patronage: Do emotional brand attachment, brand involvement, and past experience matter?</title><link>localhost:1313/docs/counterfeit-versus-original/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>localhost:1313/docs/counterfeit-versus-original/</guid><description>Skip to main content Advertisement SpringerLink
Search Log in Original Article Open Access Published: 19 March 2020
Counterfeit versus original patronage: Do emotional brand attachment, brand involvement, and past experience matter?
Xuemei Bian1 &amp;amp; Sadia Haque1
Journal of Brand Management volume 27, pages 438–451 (2020)Cite this article
✉︎ :Sadia Haque sadia.haque@northumbria.ac.uk
1: Northumbria University, Office – 417a, City Campus East 1, Newcastle upon Tyne NE1 8ST, UK
3226 Accesses 5 Citations 3 Altmetric Metrics details</description></item><item><title>ON THE ORIGIN OF CREATINE</title><link>localhost:1313/docs/creatine/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>localhost:1313/docs/creatine/</guid><description>ON THE ORIGIN OF CREATINE.1
By L. BAUMANN and J. MARKER.
(From the Laboratories Medicine, of the Departments State University of of Physiology and Internal Iowa, Iowa City.)
(Received for publication, June 12, 1915.)
The search for possible precursors of creatine has always led to a consideration of substances containing the guanidine radicle, as arginine and glycocyamine, or methylamino groups, as sarcosine, betaine, and choline.
Van Hoogenhuyze and Verploegh2 found no increase in the elimination of creatinine, after the ingestion of proteins relatively rich in arginine.</description></item><item><title>Detecting the origins of moisture over Southeast China: Seasonal variation and heavy Rainfall</title><link>localhost:1313/docs/detecting-moisture/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>localhost:1313/docs/detecting-moisture/</guid><description>ADVANCES IN ATMOSPHERIC SCIENCES, VOL. 33, MARCH 2016, 319–329 Detecting the Origins of Moisture over Southeast China: Seasonal Variation and Heavy Rainfall Xiuzhen LI1, Wen ZHOU2[^∗], and Yongqin David CHEN3
(Received 24 March 2015; revised 25 August 2015; accepted 2 September 2015)
ABSTRACT
To examine the ability of the Hybrid Single-Particle Lagrangian Integrated Trajectory (HYSPLIT) model to detect the origins and paths of moisture supplied to Southeast China, trajectories of air particles released over Southeast China were traced backward during 1 April 2012 to 31 March 2013 and three typical regional persistent heavy rainfall events.</description></item><item><title>Differentiation Between Spirits According to Their Botanical Origin</title><link>localhost:1313/docs/differentiation-spirits/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>localhost:1313/docs/differentiation-spirits/</guid><description>Food Anal. Methods (2016) 9:1029–1035 DOI 10.1007/s12161-015-0280-x
Skip to main content Advertisement SpringerLink
Search Log in Open Access Published: 16 August 2015 Differentiation Between Spirits According to Their Botanical Origin
Paulina Wiśniewska1, Magdalena Śliwińska1, Tomasz Dymerski1, Waldemar Wardencki1 &amp;amp; Jacek Namieśnik1
✉︎ Paulina Wiśniewska p.m.wisniewska@gmail.com
Food Analytical Methods volume 9, pages 1029–1035 (2016)Cite this article
Received: 11 May 2015 / Accepted: 6 August 2015 / Published online: 16 August 2015 © The Author(s) 2015.</description></item><item><title>Food taboos: their origins and purposes</title><link>localhost:1313/docs/food-taboos/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>localhost:1313/docs/food-taboos/</guid><description>Skip to main content Advertisement BMC Part of Springer Nature
Search Explore journals Get published About BMC Login Journal of Ethnobiology and Ethnomedicine Home About Articles Submission Guidelines Review Open Access Published: 29 June 2009 Food taboos: their origins and purposes
Victor Benno Meyer-Rochow12 Journal of Ethnobiology and Ethnomedicine volume 5, Article number: 18 (2009) Cite this article
Published: 29 June 2009 Received: 4 December 2008 Journal of Ethnobiology and Ethnomedicine 2009, 5:18 doi:10.</description></item><item><title>Ganges: special at its origin</title><link>localhost:1313/docs/ganges/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>localhost:1313/docs/ganges/</guid><description>Skip to main content Advertisement BMC Part of Springer Nature
Search Explore journals Get published About BMC Login Journal of Biological Research-Thessaloniki Home About Articles Submission Guidelines Letter to the Editor Open Access Published: 15 July 2016 Ganges: special at its origin
Krishna Khairnar1 Journal of Biological Research-Thessaloniki volume 23, Article number: 16 (2016) Cite this article
2024 Accesses 8 Citations 84 Altmetric Metrics details
© 2016 The Author(s). This article is distributed under the terms of the Creative Commons Attribution 4.</description></item><item><title>Given that the detailed original criteria for deliberate practice have not changed, could the understanding of this complex concept have improved over time? A response to Macnamara and Hambrick (2020)</title><link>localhost:1313/docs/given-that-detailed/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>localhost:1313/docs/given-that-detailed/</guid><description>Skip to main content Advertisement SpringerLink
Search Log in Original Article Open Access Published: 24 June 2020 Given that the detailed original criteria for deliberate practice have not changed, could the understanding of this complex concept have improved over time? A response to Macnamara and Hambrick (2020)
K. Anders Ericsson1[^*] Psychological Research volume 85, pages 1114–1120 (2021)Cite this article
[^*] ✉︎ K. Anders Ericsson ericsson@psy.fsu.edu; charness@psy.fsu.edu
2040 Accesses 2 Altmetric Metrics details</description></item><item><title>Hanwoo cattle: origin, domestication, breeding strategies and genomic selection</title><link>localhost:1313/docs/hanwoo-cattle/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>localhost:1313/docs/hanwoo-cattle/</guid><description>Skip to main content Advertisement BMC Part of Springer Nature
Search Explore journals Get published About BMC Login Journal of Animal Science and Technology logo Journal of Animal Science and Technology Articles Review Open Access Published: 15 May 2014 Hanwoo cattle: origin, domestication, breeding strategies and genomic selection
Seung-Hwan Lee1†, Byoung-Ho Park2†, Aditi Sharma1†, Chang-Gwon Dang1, Seung-Soo Lee2, Tae-Jeong Choi2, Yeon-Ho Choy2, Hyeong-Cheol Kim1, Ki-Jun Jeon1, Si-Dong Kim2, Seong-Heum Yeon1, Soo-Bong Park2 &amp;amp; Hee-Seol Kang1 Journal of Animal Science and Technology volume 56, Article number: 2 (2014) Cite this article</description></item><item><title>The developmental origins of hoarding disorder in adolescence: a longitudinal clinical interview study following an epidemiological survey</title><link>localhost:1313/docs/hoarding/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>localhost:1313/docs/hoarding/</guid><description>Skip to main content Advertisement SpringerLink
European Child &amp;amp; Adolescent Psychiatry (2021) 30:415–425 https://doi.org/10.1007/s00787-020-01527-2 ORIGINAL CONTRIBUTION
Check for updates
Search Log in The developmental origins of hoarding disorder in adolescence: a longitudinal clinical interview study following an epidemiological survey Download PDF Original Contribution Open Access Published: 18 April 2020 The developmental origins of hoarding disorder in adolescence: a longitudinal clinical interview study following an epidemiological survey
Volen Z. Ivanov1, David Mataix-Cols1, Eva Serlachius1, Gustaf Brander1, Anders Elmquist1, Jesper Enander1 &amp;amp; Christian Rück1 European Child &amp;amp; Adolescent Psychiatry volume 30, pages 415–425 (2021)Cite this article</description></item><item><title>How to write an original article for the *Journal of Orthopaedics and Traumatology*</title><link>localhost:1313/docs/how-to-write/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>localhost:1313/docs/how-to-write/</guid><description>Skip to main content Advertisement SpringerOpen
Search Get published Explore Journals Books About Login Journal of Orthopaedics and Traumatology Official Journal of the Italian Society of Orthopaedics and Traumatology
About Articles Submission Guidelines Editorial Open Access Published: 13 March 2008 Published online: 17 March 2008
J Orthopaed Traumatol (2008) 9:1–3 DOI 10.1007/s10195-008-0096-1
EDITORIAL # How to write an original article for the Journal of Orthopaedics and Traumatology
L. Pierannunzii Journal of Orthopaedics and Traumatology volume 9, pages 1–3 (2008)Cite this article</description></item><item><title>“Into and Out of” the Qinghai-Tibet Plateau and the Himalayas: Centers of origin and diversification across five clades of Eurasian montane and alpine passerine birds</title><link>localhost:1313/docs/in-out-qinghai-tibet-plateau/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>localhost:1313/docs/in-out-qinghai-tibet-plateau/</guid><description>Skip to Article Content Skip to Article Information Working off-campus? Learn about our remote access options By continuing to browse this site, you agree to its use of cookies as described in our Cookie Policy. × Wiley Online Library Login / Register Ecology and Evolution Ecology and Evolution ORIGINAL RESEARCH Open Access “Into and Out of” the Qinghai-Tibet Plateau and the Himalayas: Centers of origin and diversification across five clades of Eurasian montane and alpine passerine birds</description></item><item><title>An interview with Patrick O Brown on the origins and future of open access</title><link>localhost:1313/docs/interview-patrick-o-brown/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>localhost:1313/docs/interview-patrick-o-brown/</guid><description>Skip to main content Advertisement BMC Part of Springer Nature
Search Explore journals Get published About BMC Login BMC Biology BMC Biology logo Home About Articles Submission Guidelines Interview Open Access Published: 15 April 2013 An interview with Patrick O Brown on the origins and future of open access
Patrick O Brown1 BMC Biology volume 11, Article number: 33 (2013) Cite this article
Brown BMC Biology 2013, 11:33 http://www.biomedcentral.com/1741-7007/11/33 10th anniversary INTERVIEW Open Access</description></item><item><title>Can people identify original and manipulated photos of real-world scenes?</title><link>localhost:1313/docs/manipulated-photos/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>localhost:1313/docs/manipulated-photos/</guid><description>Skip to main content Advertisement SpringerOpen
Search Get published Explore Journals Books About Login Cognitive Research: Principles and Implications About Articles Submission Guidelines Original article Open Access Published: 18 July 2017 Can people identify original and manipulated photos of real-world scenes?
Sophie J. Nightingale*, Kimberley A. Wade &amp;amp; Derrick G. Watson Cognitive Research: Principles and Implications volume 2, Article number: 30 (2017) Cite this article
* Correspondence: S.Nightingale@warwick.ac.uk Department of Psychology, University of Warwick, Coventry CV4 7AL, UK</description></item><item><title>Neighborhoods and bands: an analysis of the origins of spam</title><link>localhost:1313/docs/neighborhood-spam/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>localhost:1313/docs/neighborhood-spam/</guid><description>Skip to main content Advertisement SpringerOpen
Search Get published Explore Journals Books About Login Journal of Internet Services and Applications a SpringerOpen Journal
About Articles Submission Guidelines Research Open Access Published: 11 May 2015 Neighborhoods and bands: an analysis of the origins of spam
Osvaldo Fonseca1*, Elverton Fazzion1, Pedro Henrique B Las-Casas1, Dorgival Guedes1, Wagner Meira Jr1, Cristine Hoepers1, Klaus Steding-Jessen2 &amp;amp; Marcelo HP Chaves2 Journal of Internet Services and Applications volume 6, Article number: 9 (2015) Cite this article</description></item><item><title>What is the origin of the ectopic beat?</title><link>localhost:1313/docs/origin-of-the-ectopic-beat/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>localhost:1313/docs/origin-of-the-ectopic-beat/</guid><description>Skip to main content SpringerLink
Log in
What is the origin of the ectopic beat? Download PDF
Rhythm Puzzle - Answer Open Access Published online: 12 February 2015 © The Author(s) 2015. This article is published with open access at Springerlink.com
What is the origin of the ectopic beat?
Netherlands Heart Journal volume 23, pages 245–246 (2015)Cite this article
770 Accesses
Metrics details
P. M. H. Nierop (✉︎) UMC Groningen, Groningen, Deutschland e-mail: p.</description></item><item><title>Origins</title><link>localhost:1313/docs/origins/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>localhost:1313/docs/origins/</guid><description>Skip to main contentSkip to article Elsevier logo Journals &amp;amp; Books Register Sign in View PDF Download full issue Outline Acknowledgments References Journal of Biological Chemistry Volume 280, Issue 24, 17 June 2005, Pages 22557-22559
Journal home page for Journal of Biological Chemistry THE JOURNAL OF BIOLOGICAL CHEMISTRY Vol. 280, No. 24, Issue of June 17, pp. 22557–22559, 2005 © 2005 by The American Society for Biochemistry and Molecular Biology, Inc.</description></item><item><title>The 5th anniversary of “Patient Safety in Surgery” – from the Journal’s origin to its future vision</title><link>localhost:1313/docs/patient-safety/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>localhost:1313/docs/patient-safety/</guid><description>Skip to main content Advertisement BMC Part of Springer Nature
Stahel et al. Patient Safety in Surgery 2012, 6:24 http://www.pssjournal.com/content/6/1/24 PATIENT SAFETY IN SURGERY
Search Explore journals Get published About BMC Login Patient Safety in Surgery Home About Articles Submission Guidelines Editorial Open Access Published: 18 October 2012 The 5th anniversary of “Patient Safety in Surgery” – from the Journal’s origin to its future vision
Philip F Stahel1,2*, Wade R Smith3, Dieter Hahnloser4, Giuseppe Nigri5, Cyril Mauffrey1 &amp;amp; Pierre-Alain Clavien6</description></item><item><title>Tracing the origins of rendang and its development</title><link>localhost:1313/docs/rendang/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>localhost:1313/docs/rendang/</guid><description>Skip to main content Advertisement BMC Part of Springer Nature
Search Explore journals Get published About BMC Login Journal of Ethnic Foods Home About Articles Submission Guidelines Original article ORIGINAL ARTICLE
Open Access Published: 01 September 2020 Tracing the origins of rendang and its development
Fadly Rahman Journal of Ethnic Foods volume 7, Article number: 28 (2020) Cite this article
5235 Accesses 1 Citations 11 Altmetric Metrics details
Correspondence: fadly.rahman@unpad.ac.id Department of History and Philology, Faculty of Cultural Sciences, Universitas Padjadjaran, Jatinangor, West Java, Indonesia</description></item><item><title>Assessing the Impact of an Original Soft Communicative Robot in a Nursing Home in Japan: Will Softness or Conversations Bring more Smiles to Older People?</title><link>localhost:1313/docs/soft-robot/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>localhost:1313/docs/soft-robot/</guid><description>Skip to main content Advertisement SpringerLink
Search Log in Open Access Published: 07 August 2021 Assessing the Impact of an Original Soft Communicative Robot in a Nursing Home in Japan: Will Softness or Conversations Bring more Smiles to Older People?
Kazuko Obayashi123, Naonori Kodate34567 &amp;amp; Shigeru Masuyama 38
Accepted: 19 July 2021 © The Author(s) 2021
International Journal of Social Robotics (2021)Cite this article
✉︎ Naonori Kodate naonori.kodate@ucd.ie
Published online: 07 August 2021 Springer</description></item><item><title>Softwaretest mit Originaldaten Eine Analyse aus Sicht des Datenschutzes</title><link>localhost:1313/docs/softwaretest-originaldaten/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>localhost:1313/docs/softwaretest-originaldaten/</guid><description>Skip to main content Advertisement SpringerLink
Search Log in SCHWERPUNKT Open Access Published: 17 February 2021 Ralf Kneuper, Sven Jacobs Softwaretest mit Originaldaten
Eine Analyse aus Sicht des Datenschutzes # Ralf Kneuper &amp;amp; Sven Jacobs Datenschutz und Datensicherheit - DuD volume 45, pages 163–167 (2021)Cite this article
288 Accesses Metrics details Zusammenfassung
Der Wunsch nach einer Nutzung von Originaldaten für den Softwaretest führt in bestimmten Konstellationen zu einem Konflikt zwischen der Zweckbeschränkung von personenbezogenen Daten einerseits und der Forderung nach Qualitätssicherung der Systeme zur Verarbeitung dieser Daten andererseits.</description></item><item><title>Origin of spectacular fields of submarine sediment waves around volcanic islands</title><link>localhost:1313/docs/spectacular-submarine/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>localhost:1313/docs/spectacular-submarine/</guid><description>Skip to main contentSkip to article Elsevier logo Journals &amp;amp; Books Register Sign in View PDF Download full issue Outline Highlights Abstract Keywords
Introduction Geologic setting Data and methods Results Discussion Conclusions Acknowledgments Appendix A. Supplementary material References Show full outline Figures (8) Fig. 1. Logarithmic plot of wavelength versus wave height for global submarine bedform… Fig. 2. Map of the study area in the Kermadec Arc, showing extent of detailed… Fig.</description></item><item><title>Urban Conservation Through Chinese Local Original Architecture: The Preservation and Renovation of Zhongshan Road in Hangzhou</title><link>localhost:1313/docs/urban-conservation/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>localhost:1313/docs/urban-conservation/</guid><description>Skip to main content Advertisement SpringerOpen
Search Menu Built Heritage About Articles Submission Guidelines Download PDF Open Access Published: 01 March 2017 Urban Conservation Through Chinese Local Original Architecture: The Preservation and Renovation of Zhongshan Road in Hangzhou
Shu Wang Built Heritage volume 1, pages 50–56 (2017)Cite this article
452 Accesses 1 Citations Metrics details
Shu Wang Department of Architecture, China Academy of Art, Hangzhou, China
ABSTRACT How to realise the goal of city revival through the preservation of historic districts is an important is- sue for all historic cities.</description></item><item><title>The Origin of Vertebrate Gills</title><link>localhost:1313/docs/vertebrate-gills/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>localhost:1313/docs/vertebrate-gills/</guid><description>Skip to main contentSkip to article Elsevier logo Journals &amp;amp; Books Register Sign in View PDF Download full issue Outline Highlights Summary Keywords Results and Discussion Experimental Procedures Author Contributions Acknowledgments References Show full outline Figures (3) Figure1. The Ecto-endobranchiate Hypothesis Figure2. Skate Gill Filaments Arise within an Endodermal Shh Expression Domain Figure3. Skate Gills Derive from Pharyngeal Endoderm Current Biology Volume 27, Issue 5, 6 March 2017, Pages 729-732 Journal home page for Current Biology</description></item><item><title>Volcanic origin of the 1741 Oshima-Oshima tsunami in the Japan Sea</title><link>localhost:1313/docs/volcanic-origin-1741/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>localhost:1313/docs/volcanic-origin-1741/</guid><description>Skip to main content Advertisement SpringerOpen Search Get published Explore Journals Books About Login Earth, Planets and Space About Articles Submission Guidelines Article Open Access
Published: 08 June 2007
Volcanic origin of the 1741 Oshima-Oshima tsunami in the Japan Sea
Kenji Satake ✉︎
Active Fault Research Center, National Institute of Advance Industrial Science and Technology, 1-1-1 Higashi, Tsukuba 305-8567, Japan
(Received September 25, 2006; Revised January 9, 2007; Accepted January 19, 2007; Online published June 8, 2007)</description></item><item><title>What is Morita Therapy? The Nature, Origins, and Cross-Cultural Application of a Unique Japanese Psychotherapy</title><link>localhost:1313/docs/what-is-morita-therapy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>localhost:1313/docs/what-is-morita-therapy/</guid><description>Skip to main content SpringerLink Log in Original Paper Open Access Published: 07 July 2020 What is Morita Therapy? The Nature, Origins, and Cross-Cultural Application of a Unique Japanese Psychotherapy
Holly V. R. Sugg1, David A. Richards1 &amp;amp; Julia Frost1
Journal of Contemporary Psychotherapy volume 50, pages 313–322 (2020) Cite this article 4846 Accesses Metrics details Abstract # Morita Therapy is a Japanese psychotherapy which contrasts with established Western approaches in teaching, through behavioural experience, that symptoms are part of the natural ecology of human experience.</description></item><item><title>Revealing the origin of wildcat reappearance after presumed long-term absence</title><link>localhost:1313/docs/wildcat-reappearance/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>localhost:1313/docs/wildcat-reappearance/</guid><description>Skip to main content Advertisement SpringerLink Search Log in Original Article Open Access Published: 29 October 2020 Revealing the origin of wildcat reappearance after presumed long-term absence
Sarah A. Mueller1,2, Tobias E. Reiners1,2, Katharina Steyer1, Alina von Thaden1,2, Annika Tiesmeyer1,2 &amp;amp; Carsten Nowak1,3
European Journal of Wildlife Research volume 66, Article number: 94 (2020)
Supplementary Information # The online version contains supplementary material available at https://doi.org/10.1007/s10344-020-01433-7.
✉︎ Sarah A. Mueller smueller@senkenberg.</description></item></channel></rss>